Ghoul Head has evolved into Mad Headder
Loading
Begin Adventure
Episode 4\h\h\h\h\h\h\hExistence Evolution
Take this!
No way!
What?!
Buff
Status Effect
Stunned
Paralysis
Heal [Support Skill]
Paralysis Heal [Support Skill]
Monster: Mad Headder
Remaining skill points: 5
Oath of the Heavy Armor
\hDefense Booster
\hBeginner Swordsmanship
Remaining skill points: 4
Remaining skill points: 3
Remaining skill points: 2
Remaining skill points: 1
Remaining skill points: 0
Beginner Swordsmanship has reached level 5
Vital Slice skill has been acquired
Vital Slice [Common Skill]
Land a heavy blow with a blade from zero distance
Effective against targets with high Defense
Vital Slice
\h\h\h\h\hDaemonsrage Shield
\h\h+25 Defense
\h\hMarket Price: 3,000,000 gold
After blocking an attack, your next
attack receives a +8 bonus
Fang of
Smoldering Insanity
Skillbook
Remaining skill points: 5
Oath of the Heavy Armor
Defense Booster
Beginner Swordsmanship